Guide to the Sara and Gerald Murphy Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Photographs, 1880-1990s; Series III; 12.84 linear feet (43 boxes)
  - Formal Portraits of Murphy and Wiborg Immediate Families
    - Individuals
      - Fish, Olga Wiborg by Rita Martin, New York, 1914 (Box 21, Folder 311)
      - Fish, Olga Wiborg, circa 1920 (Box 21, Folder 312)
      - Fish, Olga Wiborg by Demeyer, 1934 (Box 21, Folder 313)
      - Fish, Olga Wiborg, Before 1937 (Box 21, Folder 314)
      - Fish, Olga Wiborg sitting in front of Picasso painting, Before 1937
      - Fish, Stuyvesant by Jeron, Carmel, circa 1942 (Box 21, Folder 315)
      - Murphy, Anna Ryan by C.F. Conly, Boston, circa 1880 (Box 21, Folder 316)
      - Murphy, Baoth by Bachrach, New York, 1919 (Box 21, Folder 317)
      - Murphy, Baoth with toy tea set, circa 1921 (Box 21, Folder 318)
      - Murphy, Baoth by Madame Albin Guillot, Paris, circa 1923 (Box 21, Folder 319)
      - Murphy, Baoth in knight's costume by Max, Paris, circa 1925 (Box 21, Folder 320)
      - Murphy, Baoth by A. Dubost, Bad Aussee, Austria, 1931 (Box 21, Folder 321)
      - Murphy, Esther by Barbara Ker-Seymer, London, 1935 (Box 21, Folder 322)
      - Murphy, Esther by Vasari, Rome, 1949 (Box 21, Folder 323)
      - Murphy, Frederic by Histed, New York, 1914
      - Murphy, Frederic in WWI uniform, circa 1917 (Box 21, Folder 324)
      - Murphy, Frederic by André Picard, Paris, circa 1920 (Box 21, Folder 325)
      - Murphy, Gerald as boy with hands in pockets, circa 1889 (Box 21, Folder 326)
      - Murphy, Gerald by Koenig, New Brighton, Staten Island, circa 1893 (Box 21, Folder 327)
      - Murphy, Gerald by Rockwood Junior, New York, circa 1896 (Box 21, Folder 328)
      - Murphy, Gerald by Pierce, New York, circa 1900
      - Murphy, Gerald, New York, circa 1908
      - Murphy, Gerald, Yale University graduation portrait, 1912 (Box 21, Folder 329)
      - Murphy, Gerald in military uniform, circa 1916 (Box 21, Folder 330)
      - Murphy, Gerald in Norfolk jacket, circa 1922 (Box 21, Folder 331)
      - Murphy, Gerald with cigarette, Montana-Vermala, Switzerland, circa 1929 (Box 21, Folder 332)
      - Murphy, Gerald, Montana-Vermala, Switzerland, circa 1929 (Box 21, Folder 333)
      - Murphy, Gerald wearing suit and holding malacca cane and hat, 1920s (Box 21, Folder 334)
      - Murphy, Gerald, multiple exposure portrait, made into postcard by J. Weiss, Basel, Switzerland, 1930 (Box 21, Folder 335)
      - Murphy, Gerald by Lenz and Janssen Studio, New York, 1944 (Box 21, Folder 336)
      - Murphy, Gerald, passport photographs, circa 1940 (Box 21, Folder 337)
      - Murphy, Gerald, silhouettes, undated (Box 21, Folder 338)
      - Murphy, Noël Haskins by Laure Albin Guillot, Paris, 1920s (Box 21, Folder 339)
      - Murphy, Noël Haskins, various passport photographs, undated (Box 22, Folder 340)
      - Murphy, Patrick Francis, Senior by Warren's Portraits, Boston, circa 1880 (Box 22, Folder 341)
      - Murphy, Patrick Francis, Senior by Guy, Cork, circa 1890 (Box 22, Folder 342)
      - Murphy, Patrick Francis, Senior, circa 1900 (Box 22, Folder 343)
      - Murphy, Patrick Francis, passport photographs, circa 1925 (Box 22, Folder 344)
      - Murphy, Patrick Francis by Madame Albin Guillot, Paris, circa 1923 (Box 22, Folder 345)
      - Murphy, Patrick Francis, Montana-Vermala, Switzerland, circa 1929 (Box 22, Folder 346)
      - Murphy, Patrick Francis, photograph of drawing by Fernand Léger created at Saranac Lake in 1935, undated (Box 22, Folder 347)
      - Murphy, Sara Wiborg by Marceau, Cincinnati, Ohio, circa 1884 (Box 22, Folder 348)
      - Murphy, Sara Wiborg by Eagle Gallery, Des Moines, Iowa, 1886 (Box 22, Folder 349)
      - Murphy, Sara Wiborg by Marceau and Bellsmith, Cincinnati, Ohio, circa 1887 (Box 22, Folder 350)
      - Murphy, Sara Wiborg by E.B. Core, Cincinnati, Ohio, circa 1890 (Box 22, Folder 351)
      - Murphy, Sara Wiborg in hat by E.B. Core, Cincinnati, Ohio, circa 1890 (Box 22, Folder 352)
      - Murphy, Sara Wiborg holding dog, circa 1890 (Box 22, Folder 353)
      - Murphy, Sara Wiborg by Schubert and Kierulf, Berlin, Germany, circa 1898 (Box 22, Folder 354)
      - Murphy, Sara Wiborg in Dutch costume, circa 1900 (Box 22, Folder 355)
      - Murphy, Sara Wiborg, circa 1900 (Box 22, Folder 356)
      - Murphy, Sara Wiborg by F.M. Somers, Cincinnati, Ohio, 1905 (Box 22, Folder 357)
      - Murphy, Sara Wiborg, debutante portrait, circa 1905 (Box 22, Folder 358)
      - Murphy, Sara Wiborg by Keturah Collings, London, 1907
        Portrait made when Sara Murphy was presented to the Court of King Edward VII and Queen Alexandra at Buckingham Palace
      - Murphy, Sara Wiborg in feather hat by F.M. Somers, Cincinnati, Ohio, 1907-1908 (Box 22, Folder 359)
      - Murphy, Sara Wiborg seated in front of fireplace, circa 1907 (Box 22, Folder 360)
      - Murphy, Sara Wiborg seated in front of fireplace at the Dunes, circa 1910 (Box 22, Folder 361)
      - Murphy, Sara Wiborg holding dog, circa 1910 (Box 22, Folder 362)
      - Murphy, Sara Wiborg, photographs of portrait paintings, circa 1910 (Box 22, Folder 363)
      - Murphy, Sara Wiborg, engagement photograph, Dover Street Studios, London, 1915 (Box 22, Folder 364-366)
      - Murphy, Sara Wiborg in hat, Dover Street Studios, London, circa 1915 (Box 22, Folder 367)
      - Murphy, Sara Wiborg, wedding photographs, 1915 (Box 22, Folder 368)
      - Murphy, Sara Wiborg, circa 1940 (Box 22, Folder 369-370)
      - Murphy, Sara Wiborg by Conway Studios, New York, circa 1940
      - Murphy, Sara Wiborg by Associated Photographic Service and Blackstone Studios, New York, circa 1940 (Box 22, Folder 371)
      - Murphy, Sara Wiborg sitting on plaid couch holding dogs, by Carlyle Studios, New York, 1947 (Box 22, Folder 372)
      - Murphy, Sara Wiborg holding roses, possibly by Edward Rice, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 373)
      - Wiborg, Adeline Sherman by Marceau and Bellsmith, Cincinnati, Ohio, undated (Box 22, Folder 374)
      - Wiborg, Adeline Sherman by Schaub and Peterson, Des Moines, Iowa, undated (Box 22, Folder 375)
      - Wiborg, Adeline Sherman by North and Oswald, Toledo, Ohio, undated (Box 22, Folder 376)
      - Wiborg, Adeline Sherman by Davis and Sanford, New York, undated (Box 22, Folder 377-378)
      - Wiborg, Adeline Sherman in elaborate dress, undated
      - Wiborg, Adeline Sherman by E.B. Core, Cincinnati, Ohio, undated (Box 22, Folder 379)
      - Wiborg, Adeline Sherman by Marceau and Bellsmith, Cincinnati, Ohio, undated (Box 22, Folder 380)
      - Wiborg, Adeline Sherman by Carl Pietzner, Carlsbad, undated (Box 22, Folder 381)
      - Wiborg, Adeline Sherman, portrait in hat and portrait wearing off-the-shoulder dress, undated (Box 22, Folder 382)
      - Wiborg, Frank Bestow by Landy, Cincinnati, Ohio, undated (Box 22, Folder 383)
      - Wiborg, Frank Bestow by Bellsmith, Cincinnati, Ohio, circa 1898
      - Wiborg, Frank Bestow by F.M. Somers, Cincinnati, Ohio, 1906 (Box 23, Folder 384)
      - Wiborg, Frank Bestow by E.B. Core, Cincinnati, Ohio, undated (Box 23, Folder 385)
      - Wiborg, Frank Bestow by Sol. Young Studios, New York, undated (Box 23, Folder 386)
      - Wiborg, Frank Bestow by Benjamin Portraits, Cincinnati, Ohio, undated (Box 23, Folder 387)
      - Wiborg, Frank Bestow by Benjamin Portraits, Cincinnati, Ohio and engraving based on photograph by E.G. Williams and Brothers, New York, undated
      - Wiborg, Frank Bestow by Marjori, New York, undated (Box 23, Folder 388)
      - Wiborg, Frank Bestow by Elliott and Fry, London, England, undated (Box 23, Folder 389)
      - Wiborg, Frank Bestow, undated (Box 23, Folder 390)
      - Wiborg, Frank Bestow, reproduction by Hollinger and Company, undated
      - Wiborg, Frank, reproduction of a drawing, undated (Box 23, Folder 391)
      - Wiborg, Mary Hoyt by E.B. Core, Cincinnati, Ohio, circa 1889 (Box 23, Folder 392)
      - Wiborg, Mary Hoyt by R.P. Bellsmith, Cincinnati, Ohio, circa 1907 (Box 23, Folder 393)
      - Wiborg, Mary Hoyt by Lallie Charles, London, England, circa 1907 (Box 23, Folder 394)
      - Wiborg, Mary Hoyt by Kazanjian, New York, circa 1908
      - Wiborg, Mary Hoyt on horseback by Paul Thompson, New York and unidentified, circa 1910
      - Wiborg, Mary Hoyt, circa 1914 (Box 23, Folder 395)
      - Wiborg, Mary Hoyt by unidentified studio, 3, Place de la Madeleine, Paris, France, circa 1920
    - Group Portraits: Murphy Family
      - Gerald and Frederic Murphy by Partridge Studios, Cambridge, Massachusetts, 1891 (Box 23, Folder 396)
      - Gerald and Frederic Murphy by See and Epler, New York, circa 1895 (Box 23, Folder 397)
      - Gerald Murphy in sailor costume, circa 1896 (Box 23, Folder 398)
      - Gerald and Frederic Murphy by Rockwood Junior, New York, circa 1897 (Box 23, Folder 399)
      - Gerald Murphy with friends at Coney Island, circa 1912 (Box 23, Folder 400)
      - Gerald and Sara Murphy at Coney Island, circa 1916 (Box 23, Folder 401)
      - Gerald Murphy in portrait of the United States Army School of Military Aeronautics, 1918 (Box 23, Folder 402)
      - Sara Murphy holding Honoria, circa 1917 (Box 23, Folder 403)
      - Gerald Murphy in uniform holding Honoria, 1918 March (Box 23, Folder 404)
      - Case with photograph of Sara Murphy holding Honoria and portrait of Honoria, 1918 (Box 23, Folder 405)
      - Gerald Murphy holding Baoth, 1919 (Box 23, Folder 406)
      - Sara Murphy with Baoth and Honoria, 1919 (Box 23, Folder 407)
      - Gerald Murphy holding Patrick by Marshall, Cambridge, Massachusetts, circa 1920 (Box 23, Folder 408)
      - Family portrait, Cambridge, Massachusetts, circa 1920 (Box 23, Folder 409)
      - Murphy children by A. Sovignity, Photographie Victor-Hugo, Paris, circa 1921
      - Family portrait, 1922 (Box 23, Folder 410)
      - Gerald and Sara Murphy in costume at Étienne de Beaumont's "Automotive Ball" by Mondanités Dorys, 1924 (Box 23, Folder 411)
      - Murphy children, circa 1924 (Box 23, Folder 412)
        Photograph cut around the profiles and mounted on wood
      - Murphy children by Vallois, Paris, France, circa 1924 (Box 23, Folder 413)
      - Murphy children by Lee Miller, Paris, France, circa 1925 (Box 23, Folder 414)
      - Murphy children with unidentified boy by J. Sanitas, Cannes, circa 1925 (Box 23, Folder 415)
        Photograph cut around the profiles and mounted on plastic
      - Murphy family by Man Ray, France, 1926 (Box 23, Folder 416)
      - Murphy children by Man Ray, France, 1926 (Box 23, Folder 417)
      - Murphy children, passport photographs, circa 1926 (Box 23, Folder 418)
      - Murphy children, passport photographs, Antibes, France, 1929 August (Box 23, Folder 419)
      - Baoth Murphy and Patrick Murphy, dressed up as policeman and cowboy, circa 1929 (Box 23, Folder 420)
      - Murphy children shipboard by Ella Barnett, New York, circa 1929 (Box 23, Folder 421)
      - Sara Murphy with children, circa 1929 (Box 23, Folder 422)
      - Sara Murphy and Honoria in carnival cut-outs as if riding horses, circa 1930 (Box 23, Folder 423)
      - Sara Murphy and Honoria by Marc Le Nois, Cannes, France, circa 1930 (Box 24, Folder 424)
      - Gerald Murphy and Patrick, Montana-Vermala, Switzerland, circa 1930 (Box 24, Folder 425)
      - Family portrait, Bad Aussee, Austria, 1931 (Box 24, Folder 426-428)
      - Murphy children, passport photographs, circa 1931 (Box 24, Folder 429)
      - Baoth and Honoria in green leather frame, circa 1932 (Box 24, Folder 430)
      - Patrick and Honoria in blue frame, circa 1932 (Box 24, Folder 431)
      - Honoria in theatre productions by Alfredo Valente, circa 1935 (Box 24, Folder 432)
      - Honoria, John Shelton, and friends at a dinner party by Friedman-Engeler, New York, circa 1943 (Box 24, Folder 433)
      - Honoria with John Donnelly, circa 1952 (Box 24, Folder 434)
      - Donnelly children, circa 1960 (Box 24, Folder 435)
      - Honoria with William Donnelly by Jill Krementz, New York, 1976 September (Box 24, Folder 436)
    - Group Portraits: Wiborg Family
      - Adeline and Frank Wiborg with others by C.G. Rude, Drammen, Norway, circa 1882 (Box 24, Folder 437)
      - Adeline and Frank Wiborg holding tennis rackets with others, circa 1882 (Box 24, Folder 438)
      - Adeline and baby (possibly Sara) by Boyd, Des Moines, Iowa, circa 1883 (Box 24, Folder 439)
      - Wiborg family at Fourth of July party in a park, 1889 July 4 (Box 24, Folder 440)
      - Sara and Mary Hoyt in studio beach scene, circa 1889 (Box 24, Folder 441)
      - Matted portraits of Sara, Mary Hoyt, and Olga, by E.B. Core, Cincinnati, Ohio, circa 1890 (Box 24, Folder 442)
      - Wiborg family by E.B. Core, Cincinnati, Ohio, circa 1891, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 443-444)
        Includes framed photograph (other side of frame contains photograph of Laura Donnelly's wedding)
      - Wiborg family by E.B. Core, Cincinnati, Ohio, circa 1891, 1984 (Box 25, Folder 445)
      - Sara and Mary Hoyt by E.B. Core, Cincinnati, Ohio, circa 1891 (Box 25, Folder 446)
      - Wiborg family in horse-drawn carriage, Clifton, Cincinnati, Ohio, circa 1891 (Box 25, Folder 447)
      - Wiborg girls on horseback by Rombach & Groene, Cincinnati, Ohio, circa 1895 (Box 25, Folder 448)
      - Wiborg girls in S.M.S. Hohenzollern hats by Carl Pietzner, Carlsbad, Czech Republic, 1897-1898 (Box 25, Folder 449)
      - Wiborg girls by Carl Pietzner, Carlsbad, Czech Republic, 1897-1898 (Box 25, Folder 450)
      - Wiborg girls in costume (Olga as Pierrot, Sara as Chinese empress, and Mary Hoyt as Dutch girl) by Bellsmith, Cincinnati, Ohio, circa 1899 (Box 25, Folder 451)
      - Frank Wiborg and others greeting Prince Henry of Prussia (?) by Benjamin Studio Grand, Cincinnati, Ohio, circa 1903 (Box 25, Folder 452)
      - Mary Hoyt in theatre production/musical burlesque with A. Goldberg and Mrs. Chas. Dana Gibson by Paul Thompson, East Hampton, New York, circa 1906 (Box 25, Folder 453)
      - Wiborg sisters by Pierce, New York, 1908
      - Wiborg girls seated in front of tapestry possibly at the Dunes by Pierce, New York, circa 1909
      - Wiborg sisters as bridesmaids in Sara Sherman Mitchell's wedding, 1910 July (Box 25, Folder 454)
      - Wiborg family riding elephants, Jaipur, India, 1914 (Box 25, Folder 455)
      - Olga's wedding with Sara and Mary Hoyt as bridesmaids by Mr. and Mrs. Bradey, New York, 1915 (Box 25, Folder 456)
      - Mary Hoyt in Junior League show, New York, 1916 (Box 25, Folder 457)
        Also in photograph are Helen Hamilton Woods and Katherine Barnes
      - Adeline and Frank Wiborg by Bettini Syndicate Inc., New York, Before 1917 (Box 25, Folder 458)
      - Mary Hoyt in nurse's uniform with Mrs. Squires by Georges Dart, Montmirail, France, circa 1918 (Box 25, Folder 459)
      - Frank Wiborg with John Drew by Carl Klein, New York, circa 1920 (Box 25, Folder 460)
      - Olga with husband Sidney Fish and son Stuyvesant Fish by Julian P. Graham, 1925 (Box 25, Folder 461)
      - Fish, Olga Wiborg with son Stuyvesant Fish, photograph of an oil painting, undated (Box 25, Folder 462)
  - Formal Portraits of Extended Family and Friends
    - Allen, Henry T., undated (Box 26, Folder 463)
    - Barry, Ellen and Philip, undated (Box 26, Folder 464)
    - Benchley, Robert with dog, on stage, and smoking with Marc Connelly, undated (Box 26, Folder 465-466)
    - Campbell, Patrick (Stella), Mrs., undated (Box 26, Folder 467-468)
      Various publicity shots including one of Campbell in Summer Theatre production in Connecticut
    - Clemenceau, Georges, undated (Box 26, Folder 469)
    - Dos Passos, John with family, 1953, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 470)
      Various Christmas card photographs
    - Dos Passos, Lucy, circa 1952-1970 (Box 26, Folder 471)
    - Durante, Jimmie with Lou Clayton and Ed Jackson, cartoon postcard for "Just for a Laugh at the Parody Restaurant", undated (Box 26, Folder 472)
    - MacLeish, Ada, 1950s (Box 26, Folder 473)
    - MacLeish, Archibald with basket of peaches, portrait by The Sunday Bulletin, Philadelphia, and portrait by unidentified photographer, undated (Box 26, Folder 474)
    - Miles, Nelson A., circa 1900 (Box 26, Folder 475-476)
    - Mitchell, Ledyard and Sara Sherman with family, 1940s (Box 26, Folder 477)
    - Orloff, Vladimir in sailor's cap, undated (Box 26, Folder 478)
    - Parker, Dorothy photographed by George Platt Lynes, undated (Box 26, Folder 479)
    - Peto, Ruby with family, undated (Box 26, Folder 480)
    - Pickman, David and Betsy, undated (Box 26, Folder 481)
    - Porter, Cole, headshot and in carnival cutout as matador, undated (Box 26, Folder 482)
    - Porter, Cole, photograph of drawing by Melik of Cole at a piano with the score for "Kiss Me Kate", 1953 (Box 26, Folder 483)
    - Revello, Baptistine, undated (Box 26, Folder 484)
    - Rubenstein, Arthur, undated (Box 26, Folder 485)
    - Seldes, Gilbert, undated (Box 26, Folder 486)
    - Sherman family, undated (Box 26, Folder 487)
    - Sherman, Helen by Max Platz, Chicago, undated (Box 26, Folder 488)
    - Sherman, Hoyt, engraving by E.G. Williams and Brothers, New York, undated (Box 26, Folder 489)
    - Sherman, John by Rockwood, 1885
    - Sherman, Moulton Hoyt, Mrs. by J.J. Wolfe, Lancaster, Ohio, undated (Box 26, Folder 490)
    - Sherman, Nellie Hoyt, 1891 August (Box 26, Folder 491)
    - Sherman, William Tecumseh photograph and engravings by J.C. Curdy and Co., Philadelphia and William Sartain, Philadelphia, 1888 and 1883 (Box 26, Folder 492)
    - Tolstoy, Ilya and Beatrice Stewart, carnival cutout so appear to be riding a dolphin, undated (Box 26, Folder 493)
    - William II, German Emperor with family by J.C. Schaarwächter, Berlin and headshot by W. Kuntzen, Baden-Baden, England, 1898 and undated (Box 26, Folder 494-495)
    - Wiborg, Grace and unidentified by Gilbert Temple, Clinton, Iowa, undated (Box 26, Folder 496)
      Cousins of Frank Wiborg
    - Wiborg, Henry and Susan, undated (Box 26, Folder 497)
    - Wiborg, Susan, undated (Box 26, Folder 498)
    - Wiborg, Susan with Frank and Harry Wiborg, undated
    - Woolley, Monty, portraits and postcards of Woolley in feathered hat standing next to and driving a car, undated (Box 26, Folder 499)
    - Various photographs of Noël Haskins Murphy's ancestors, undated (Box 26, Folder 500)
    - Unidentified, undated (Box 26, Folder 501-504)
    - Unidentified, circa 1850-1940 (Box 27, Folder 505-507)
  - Snapshots and Candid Portraits
    - Gerald Murphy as baby and young boy, 1888, circa1896 (Box 27, Folder 508)
      Photographs sent from Gerald Murphy to Sara Wiborg Murphy circa 1914
    - Wiborg girls in Clifton, Cincinnati, Ohio, circa 1889 (Box 27, Folder 509)
    - Wiborg girls on steps of home in Clifton, Cincinnati, Ohio, circa 1890 (Box 27, Folder 510)
    - Sara Murphy Wiborg with caption "My Little School -- Clifton", circa 1890 (Box 27, Folder 511)
    - Wiborg family at home, Clifton, Cincinnati, Ohio, circa 1890 (Box 27, Folder 512)
    - Wiborg girls outside of home in Clifton, Cincinnati, Ohio, circa 1894 (Box 27, Folder 513)
    - Photographs of Kaiser Wilhelm in military regalia, circa 1898 (Box 27, Folder 514)
    - Wiborg girls during visit to Germany, 1898 (Box 27, Folder 515)
    - Gerald Murphy as a boy playing polo, 1898 (Box 27, Folder 516)
      Includes "tiny Kodaks" sent by Anna Ryan Murphy to Sara Murphy in 1915
    - Wiborg family having a picnic, circa 1900 (Box 27, Folder 517)
    - Photograph of pipeline possibly taken by Frank Wiborg on his travels in South America, circa 1905 (Box 27, Folder 518)
    - Unidentified man standing in front of home in East Hampton, Long Island, New York, 1906 August (Box 27, Folder 519)
    - Wiborgs and Murphys, East Hampton, Long Island, New York, circa 1910 (Box 27, Folder 520)
    - Gerald Murphy (photograph in blue leather Mark Cross Vienna case), circa 1910 (Box 27, Folder 521)
    - Gerald Murphy with Mandolin Club, Yale University, circa 1908 (Box 27, Folder 522)
    - Gerald Murphy in costume while attending Yale University, circa 1912 (Box 27, Folder 523)
    - Gerald Murphy while attending Yale University, group of unidentified people picnicking, and garden, circa 1912 (Box 27, Folder 524)
    - Frederic Murphy at Wiborg estate, East Hampton, New York, 1915, undated (Box 27, Folder 525)
    - Frederic Murphy in France during WWI and unidentified woman, 1917-1918 (Box 27, Folder 526)
      Includes photographs from Noël Haskins Murphy's scrapbook; photographs of Frederic Murphy and other soldiers on battlefield; Frederic Murphy recovering from injuries
    - Gerald Murphy and the Fifth Company during WWI, circa 1917
    - Gerald Murphy in uniform and Sara Murphy standing next to cannon, circa 1917 (Box 27, Folder 527)
    - Gerald and Sara with Honoria, East Hampton, New York, 1917 (Box 27, Folder 528)
    - Gerald and Sara with Honoria, New York, 1917-1918 (Box 27, Folder 529-530)
      Photographs of Honoria in crib, pram, and on carriage ride in Central Park
    - Various photographs of home and property in Topsfield, Massachusetts, circa 1919-1920 (Box 27, Folder 531)
    - Exterior and interior photographs of Murphys' home in Cambridge, Massachusetts, 1919-1920 (Box 27, Folder 532)
    - Sara, Honoria, and Baoth, Litchfield, Connecticut, 1920 Summer (Box 27, Folder 533-535)
      Includes photograph of interior of the Murphy's Litchfield home the "Glebe"
    - Honoria and Baoth Murphy in garden, 1921 April-May (Box 28, Folder 536)
    - Honoria and Baoth Murphy, Croyde Bay, England, 1921 August (Box 28, Folder 537)
    - Print of apartment building and view from Murphy's apartment, 25 Quai des Grands-Augustins, Paris, France, 1921 (Box 28, Folder 538)
    - Murphy children with nanny Henriette Géron, Rue Greuze, Paris, France, 1921 October (Box 28, Folder 539)
    - Murphy family, Houlgate, France, 1922 June (Box 28, Folder 540)
      Includes photograph of children with Monty Woolley
    - Murphy children with Sara and nanny, Parc de Versailles, France, 1922 October and 1923 (Box 28, Folder 541-542)
    - Murphy children, circa 1923 (Box 28, Folder 543)
    - Murphy family, Antibes, France, 1923 (Box 28, Folder 544-548)
      Includes photographs of Pablo Picasso, Olga Picasso and Paulo Picasso, Señora Maria Ruiz, de Lagrange children, Mrs. H.G. Squires, Count Étienne de Beaumont, Countess Édith de Beaumont, Rue Carpenter, Ginny Carpenter, Gilbert Seldes on La Garoupe beach and at the Hotel du Cap d'Antibes; includes photographs of the "Mad Beach Party"
    - Gerald and Sara with Cole Porter and Linda Porter, Venice, Italy, 1923 August (Box 28, Folder 549)
      Includes photograph of Sir Charles Mendl on the beach with Gerald Murphy and Cole Porter
    - Murphy family, Antibes, France, 1924 (Box 28, Folder 550)
      Includes photographs of Ada and Archibald MacLeish's children and Gilbert Seldes
    - Murphy family with Patrick Murphy (Senior), Frank Wiborg, and Vladimir Orloff, Saint-Cloud, France, 1924 Easter (Box 28, Folder 551)
    - Frederic Murphy and Noël Haskins Murphy in France following WWI, before 1924 (Box 28, Folder 552)
    - Sara with Honoria, Baoth, and Patrick, Chateau-d'Oex, Switzerland, 1925 January (Box 28, Folder 553)
    - Murphy children in sailor costumes, circa 1925 (Box 28, Folder 554)
    - Baoth and Patrick Murphy with nanny Henriette Géron, New York City and East Hampton, New York, 1926 September-December (Box 28, Folder 555)
      Includes photographs of boys sledding and building hunting blinds
    - Honoria on horseback, circa 1925 (Box 28, Folder 556)
    - Vladimir Orloff with crew of the Picaflor, circa 1925 (Box 28, Folder 557)
    - Murphy family, Antibes, France, 1925-1926 (Box 28, Folder 558)